Somei
Family Grave
Wait, did Dad actually like sake?
Nah, not at all.
He was even more of a chicken than you.
I think he didn't wanna drink
'cuz he was scared of hangovers.
I'm gonna be older than
he was before long...
Yep. Plus, Kyosuke was
19 when he got married.
That's only a year away for me...
I can't even picture it.
Wait a sec...
Are you wearin' makeup?
Wh-What if I am?
You don't even look that different.
If you're gonna do it, you
oughta really get painted up!
Hell no! What are you even talkin' about?!
That was a real close one.
Good thing the makeup job managed to
fool him about how banged up I was.
A Pet that Becomes Unruly as It Grows
Your face will heal soon enough,
but what happened to the tooth you lost?
Well, I saw a dentist this morning,
and they said they should be able to fix it.
That's a relief.
I'll see about finding
a dentist in Tokyo too.
Oh, let me carry that for you.
No! Thank you!
You two seem pretty happy
about keeping this quiet,
but if you get carried away,
Renji-san will see right through you.
You'll want to keep that in mind.
Right. Sorry.
Granted, someone seems angrier than I am.
Oh, Shoma? I already apologized to him, too.
You reckon he's still mad?
I ain't mad. And you oughta
stop runnin' your mouth.
You finally open your mouth
and it's to pick a fight?
You delinquents are so much trouble.
That's real rich, comin' from you.
A monkey in heat behaves better.
Oh my.
I'm really curious how a ****boy such
as yourself can be such a hypocrite.
Osakan men are just so awful.
Put a sock in it you worn
out meat****** of a ****.
Take your loose ass back to Kyoto already.
Don't mind them. They always do this.
Really?
Ever since the first time Tsubaki
came over and met Shoma.
What're you? Some kinda exhibitionist?
If you're looking, then have
the decency to get hard.
Oh, Yoshino.
You had a loose eyelash.
Whoa, whoa....
Oh my, how immature.
I agree.
Shoma-kun, too, but mostly you.
I'm Miyama Kirishima.
It's nice to meet you all.
Pleased to meet you!
Gotta say, kid... you seriously
look exactly like Gaku.
It's kinda creepin' me out.
Don't be like that. It's rude.
Think about it. To me,
it feels like one of my old pals is
trying to seduce my granddaughter.
Ain't that right, Tsubaki?
It certainly is.
Don't agree with him every single time.
So, you love Yoshino?
Yes, I do.
Stop!
I'm confident I love Yoshino more
than anyone in the entire world.
What the hell's
this little shit sayin'?
Dude's got more guts than a pod of whales.
This is makin' me thirsty.
How about you? Want a beer?
Nah, nah. He probably don't drink, anyway.
Wait, who doesn't drink?!
Me?
How'd you know that?
Kid's gramps is a real teetotaler.
His poison is sugar.
Gramps...
Wait, you mean Boss Miyama?
You two sound really close.
That reminds me of the time I
borrowed the first car he bought,
without tellin' him, and crashed
it right into a river.
Oh, shit!
What the hell is wrong with you?!
I'm tellin' you, it was a total accident!
So what I did was take the side
mirror off it and stuck it to a bike
that was left by a pachinko
joint and returned that to him.
You're outta your damn mind!
So, what happened?
Same kinda reaction.
Then, once he got done laughin' his
head off, he beat the shit outta me.
Hahahahaha
Auuuugh!
Thud
Smack
I dunno what it is, but guy's always been
real great at fightin' and gamblin'.
Hell, I can't even beat him
at rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors?!
Dude, did you...?
Welcome, sir!
Hey, there you are.
Sorry about being late.
Aw, forget about it.
Yoshino, I got some
business to take care of.
Tell the boys to wrap it
up once it gets late.
Don't wanna bother the neighbors.
Okay.
Do you have a minute?
Come by the basement, later.
Ready.
Pardon me.
Hey, sorry to drag you down here.
Oh, it's quite all right.
Pretty sweet setup, right?
Air conditioned and soundproofed!
Dunno if it's improved
my game at all, though.
Don't pay the blood no mind.
Shoma was down here earlier.
Care to explain that scar by your eye?
I got into a bit of a fight with Shoma-san.
Yeah? What for?
Nothing major, but we got into
an argument about it.
Shoma said the same thing.
Wouldn't say anything else, either.
What were you up to in
the city, the other day?
Someone had a personal vendetta with me.
We managed to talk it out, though.
And it had to happen in Osaka?
I'm sorry, sir.
Tell me about this personal vendetta.
Some associates of that girl from
Akaza Enterprises were still around.
That dumbass kid from the big talent
agency was involved too, right?
He was a separate issue—one
involving an old girl of mine.
You got no shortage of trouble, do ya, kid?
And Yoshino sniffin' around, was that
because of this stuff you were gettin' up to?
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
You think you're real clever, don't ya?
Took care of all the evidence in the park.
None of my guys were able to
find anything that mattered,
even on the surveillance footage.
You're old hat at this, huh?
Only had tea, earlier, too...
'Cuz you knew you were gonna be puking.
Makes me wonder how Gaku raised you...
So, you insist this was some personal thing?
It's the truth.
And Yoshino wasn't involved?
No, sir.
Damn, kid. You really are just like Gaku.
Talk about an awkward pair.
Kyosuke dyin' put a lid
on things for a while...
But I'm losin' my patience, here.
I'll have to settle for you, though.
Look after Yoshino.
Of course.
Did you tell Shoma-kun how you're
dating Kirishima-kun, now?
Considering how recently I saw you,
I didn't think the two of you
would be going out already.
I mean, we're "going out," but only
because I lost at rock, paper, scissors...
And get this, I think he
knew he was gonna win!
How cheap is that?!
Still, that was the deal, right?
What does it even mean to go out, anyway?
Well, in my case, it means
dating, kissing, and sex.
Relax. Knowing Kirishima-kun,
he won't do anything you're
uncomfortable with.
Y-Yeah, you're right.
He wouldn't do stuff like that.
Don't let him wrap you around
his little finger, though.
In baseball terms, Kirishima-kun is a pro,
and you don't even know
how to pick up a ball.
What are you talking about?
He seems like the type to gradually
tighten the noose over time, I think.
He's a bit like a door-to-door salesman
who charms his way into your house.
A salesman?
Do you
have a minute?
Once he's inside, it's all over, and you end up
signing a contract just from listening to him talk.
It won't
take long!
I just need your
signature here!
I'll be there to
support you every
waking moment!
Now you'll have
security for life!
Contract...?
W-Well, it'll be fine.
He's got other girls, so...
Does he, now?
What?
Yoshino-chan... Could you kiss
or have sex with a guy like him?
Wh-What're you askin' for?!
He seems to me like the kind of guy
who's honest with his desires.
And yet, he's pretty charming on top of that.
That's a pretty nasty combination.
You take him in because he seems harmless,
but once he's fully grown,
he devours you whole.
I mighta made the right move
goin' out with him, then.
It's not like I did it for love's sake.
What are you getting at?
Think about yesterday.
When I'm around, Shoma never gets violent,
no matter how pissed off he is.
The issue is Kirishima.
Huh? Where is he, anyway?
Hey there. Can I get one of those?
Give it back.
Stop Smoking
She tells you to quit, but gives
you a lighter as a present.
How very Yoshino.
These taste like shit.
I'm going out with Yoshino now.
We're dating.
You finally lose your mind?
I'm officially taking over your old job.
I can only imagine how much
a relief that must be.
What job?
You have to have noticed. There's
always someone near Yoshino.
It used to be Boss Somei's
favorite, Hotei Taketo.
Once he moved up in the
business, it was you.
And with you not being in Osaka, it's now me.
What're you gettin' at?
Have you ever wondered why Boss Somei
is so desperate to protect Yoshino?
Naw.
Wow, they really raised you
to be loyal, didn't they?
It'd pay to be a little bit skeptical.
You might realize that they're using you.
So stupid.
How's that?
Neither me nor the guys in
the family are being used.
We do it because we wanna.
You're the only one who thinks
that, you little shit.
But that's only because
you've been indoctrinated.
Think about how you're not even willing to
punch a little shit like me around Yoshino.
Just like a well-trained dog.
Won't do a thing without
your master's permission.
Nah, that's you.
You run your mouth thinkin' you're clever,
but all it sounds like is the
buzzin' of a fly by my ear.
And who tries to slug a fly?
Considerin' it's an insect, that's
a waste of time and energy.
If I'm an insect, you could always kill me.
How about you try that?
Right here, right now.
She chose me. Not you.
That means I win.
You talkin' about winnin' and losin'
shows how off mark you are.
She don't belong to me or you, dumbass.
You do realize that's loser talk, right?
What're you doing?
I have to return the GPS I planted
on Kirishima since it's a rental,
so I asked Shoma to drop it off.
If he's still got it...
Aw hell, it's a local park.
I got a bad feelin' about this.
Would you mind comin' with me?
What for?
For a raid.
Let's end this.
I borrowed these from the kitchen.
What now? You're free to run away.
You steal from someone's house
and still talk big? Dickhead.
You've gotta realize there's no one in the
damn world who'd love a prick like you.
I don't care as long as I have Yoshino.
What the hell...
...are you two doin'?!
Ow!
Yoshino!
D... Dying...
Are you okay, Yoshino?
Let me see your ankle.
Go find the buttons.
Buttons?
Buttons from your shirts came loose.
Go find them already!
This what you wanted, Yoshino-chan?
Thanks.
You found the buttons? Good.
Now take your shirts off.
Our shirts? Why?
What do you mean, why?
You tore the damn buttons off.
Good. Now swap shirts,
and sew the buttons back on.
Have you done this before?
Yep.
Because Shoma was always
gettin' into fights...
Ding
dong!
Excuse me! There was a fight with your
son and a button came loose!
If any uniforms got damaged, I made
him go to the house of the other guy,
and had 'em fix each other's shirts.
It made him stop fightin' so
he wouldn't have to do that.
Sounds like a lot of work...
So start sewin'. Now.
Wow, ignoring me?
That takes some real guts.
You probably picked this fight, didn't you?
Did Shoma do somethin' to you?
He didn't, did he?
Okay then, Shoma, flick me in the forehead.
Just do it. Hard as you can.
Dude, not that hard!
You said to do it, Yoshino-san.
Kirishima, every time you ignore a question,
I'm gonna have Shoma hit me like that.
Got it?
This is what I'm talking about.
What is?
I wouldn't hit you, Yoshino.
I told him to do it.
And I still wouldn't.
I just don't get him.
How could he say your outfit
from two days ago was whatever?
Get a load of this outfit!
The top and dress together
were only 3,000 yen!
What a find, right? Isn't it cute?
Yep, it's cute.
Whatever.
It's obviously not whatever.
It's clearly cute!
Are you crazy or something?
You don't get to say that
about other people.
Y'know what? Never mind!
My point is, you started this, right?
I guess I did.
What did you say to Shoma?
I wanted to let him know we're going out now.
I thought that would make things clear.
I'm the one you chose.
Don't go around puttin' me on the
same level as a scumbag like you.
Enough already! Pipe down.
Kirishima, do you understand why
I agreed to go out with you?
Because I won our bet.
That was just the method.
It was because I figured that sooner
or later, we would end up going out.
What do you mean?
You keep gettin' on Shoma's case.
I dunno if it's jealousy or whatever,
but Shoma's obviously known me longer,
and we lived together, and there's
nothin' anybody can do about that.
So I figured, givin' you the spot of
"boyfriend" would help even things out,
but now I find you here pickin'
fights in spite of that.
You're my boyfriend because of Shoma.
Get that straight.
What? You got a problem?
Of course not.
Whatever.
Tsubaki, sorry, but could you
and Kirishima head back first?
I gotta talk to Shoma for a sec.
Yoshino...
You shut up and go. We'll talk about
this when we're back in Tokyo.
Yoshino-chan understands
better than you think.
You were trying to cover up how
Renji-san beat you, right?
I can see why you'd want
to do something about that,
considering he's her grandfather.
Was I too obvious?
No. But you don't need to do that
sort of thing for Yoshino-chan.
If anything, you're being too secretive.
What do you mean?
Well, you want her to
take an interest in you,
yet you're hiding so much from her.
But that won't work.
You're expecting too much.
I'm not trying to hide things from her.
Oh, you didn't even realize it?
That might be even worse.
Well, in that case,
try calling her to your room.
My room?
Sure. After school one day,
have your girlfriend over to your room,
study for exams together...
Maybe go over your yearbooks.
How's that sound?
A pretty typical high school date, right?
Other people's love lives are so much fun!
Ugh, even your undershirt's busted...
What're you so pissed for?
It ain't like I'm marryin' him.
I'm fed up with how stupid this all is.
Your whole approach is nuts.
You're just givin' him cause
to get fulla himself.
S-Stupid...
I almost killed him.
Then I made the right call, stoppin' you!
Hey, you had a girlfriend, right?
I'm just curious.
I think we broke up a little while ago.
What? Again?
How's any of this matter?
I'm just thinkin', dating somebody...
How's it even work?
This is what I mean about bein' stupid.
So, if I actually liked Kirishima,
it'd be different?
Come on, don't clam up.
Think about it. What kinda guy
would even satisfy our people?
Who the hell am I supposed to marry?
Someone who can kill me.
What? Do you like me or something?
I mean, you keep makin' crazy demands...
Gross.
Shut up! I was jokin'!
There, it's fixed.
Although, I gotta say...
Life with you wouldn't be so bad.
Get a decent-paying job,
and if we both saved up,
we'd probably be okay in old age.
Sounds good to me.
Livin' with you would probably
be pretty fun, y'know?
What?
If we were gonna do that,
you'd hafta quit smokin'.
Come on, answer me!